To spare him temporarily
Я временно отпустил его
Was because your son wanted to catch more traitors
потому что хотел выследить остальных мятежников
You have such thoughts
У тебя ещё есть такое настроение
Father, please investigate
Отец мудро судит
Yu Gong, as Chancellor of the Imperial Academy
Юй Гун будучи главой Академии
Meets many students each year
ежегодно контактирует с множеством студентов
Who knows if among them
Не исключено что среди них
There aren't accomplices he incited
есть его единомышленники
Catching traitors
Борьба с мятежом
Must not leave roots
требует выкорчевывать зло с корнями
Your son spared him first
Я отпустил его
To observe secretly
чтобы в тени выследить
And root out accomplices
соратников
Unfortunately
Жаль
Last night's action by the Imperial City Guard
Увы действия дворцовой стражи прошлой ночью
Alerted the snake
вспугнули их
Ruined your son's carefully laid plans
все мои тщательные планы
All for naught
и все мои старания пошли прахом
The Imperial City Guard has always been commanded by your elder brother
Королевскую стражу всегда возглавлял твой старший брат
So you're saying
Значит
Your elder brother ruined your plan?
Значит он разрушил твои планы
No
Ни в коем случае
This matter
Это дело
Surely has nothing to do with elder brother
Я уверен брат здесь ни при чём
It must be his subordinates
Возможно ктото из его подчинённых
Acting on their own
самовольно вмешался
Elder brother perhaps
Брат скорее всего
Was just coerced by the Chen family
лишь стал жертвой влияния рода Чэнь
Then you
А ты
Aren't you also coerced by the Xie family?
Тебя тоже ведут за собой люди из клана Се
Eliminate all those present at the tavern
Всех присутствовавших в ресторане устранить
Cut ties with Yu Gong
Связь с Юй Гуном разорвана
Ensure this matter
Так мы гарантируем
Does not touch you at all
что дело не коснётся вас Ваше Высочество
Your son dares not
Сын не смеет
Your son only obeys Father
Сын слушается только отца